{
  "listado": [
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "River|Plate",
      "pregunta": "1",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Napoli",
      "pregunta": "2",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Barcelona",
      "pregunta": "3",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Valencia",
      "pregunta": "4",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Bayer|Munich",
      "pregunta": "5",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Roma",
      "pregunta": "6",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Cruz|Azul",
      "pregunta": "7",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Real|Madrid",
      "pregunta": "8",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Racing|Club",
      "pregunta": "9",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "San Pablo",
      "pregunta": "10",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Gremio",
      "pregunta": "11",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Atletico|de Madrid",
      "pregunta": "12",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Borussia|Dortmund",
      "pregunta": "13",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Milan",
      "pregunta": "14",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Manchester|City",
      "pregunta": "15",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Colo Colo",
      "pregunta": "16",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Inter de|Porto Alegre",
      "pregunta": "17",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Once|Caldas",
      "pregunta": "18",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Manchester|United",
      "pregunta": "19",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Cruzeiro",
      "pregunta": "20",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Atletico|Nacional",
      "pregunta": "21",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Lazio",
      "pregunta": "22",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Chelsea",
      "pregunta": "23",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Wolfsburgo",
      "pregunta": "24",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "San Lorenzo",
      "pregunta": "25",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Flamengo",
      "pregunta": "26",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Hamburgo",
      "pregunta": "27",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Sevilla",
      "pregunta": "28",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Juventus",
      "pregunta": "29",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Arsenal",
      "pregunta": "30",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Bayer|Leverkusen",
      "pregunta": "31",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Lanus",
      "pregunta": "32",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Osasuna",
      "pregunta": "33",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "America",
      "pregunta": "34",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Inter de|Milan",
      "pregunta": "35",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Malaga",
      "pregunta": "36",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Liverpool",
      "pregunta": "37",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Schalke 04",
      "pregunta": "38",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Torino",
      "pregunta": "39",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Everton",
      "pregunta": "40",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Universidad|de chile",
      "pregunta": "41",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Estudiantes|de la plata",
      "pregunta": "42",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Sampdoria",
      "pregunta": "43",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Velez|Sarsfield",
      "pregunta": "44",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Betis",
      "pregunta": "45",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Siena",
      "pregunta": "46",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Necaxa",
      "pregunta": "47",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "West|Bromwich",
      "pregunta": "48",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Perugia",
      "pregunta": "49",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Villareal",
      "pregunta": "50",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Herta|Berlin",
      "pregunta": "51",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Rosario|Central",
      "pregunta": "52",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Santos",
      "pregunta": "53",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Millonarios",
      "pregunta": "54",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Universidad|Catolica",
      "pregunta": "55",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Fiorentina",
      "pregunta": "56",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Atlas",
      "pregunta": "57",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Tottenham|Hotspur",
      "pregunta": "58",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Palmeiras",
      "pregunta": "59",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Werder|Bremen",
      "pregunta": "60",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Bologna",
      "pregunta": "61",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Newcastle",
      "pregunta": "62",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Levante",
      "pregunta": "63",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Palermo",
      "pregunta": "64",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Tigre",
      "pregunta": "65",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Junior de|Barranquilla",
      "pregunta": "66",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "corinthians",
      "pregunta": "67",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Fluminense",
      "pregunta": "68",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Newells|Old Boys",
      "pregunta": "69",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Deportivo|Cali",
      "pregunta": "70",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "West|Ham",
      "pregunta": "71",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Monterrey",
      "pregunta": "72",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "chievo|verona",
      "pregunta": "73",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Aston|Villa",
      "pregunta": "74",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Empoli",
      "pregunta": "75",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Vasco da|Gama",
      "pregunta": "76",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "America|de Cali",
      "pregunta": "77",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Colon",
      "pregunta": "78",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Gimnasia|de la plata",
      "pregunta": "79",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Parma",
      "pregunta": "80",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Banfield",
      "pregunta": "81",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Rayo|Vallecano",
      "pregunta": "82",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "olympique|de marsella",
      "pregunta": "83",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Genoa",
      "pregunta": "84",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Independiente|santa fe",
      "pregunta": "85",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Real|Sociedad",
      "pregunta": "86",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Fulham",
      "pregunta": "87",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Independiente|de avellaneda",
      "pregunta": "88",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Stuttgart",
      "pregunta": "89",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Espanyol de|Barcelona",
      "pregunta": "90",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Hellas|Verona",
      "pregunta": "91",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Union",
      "pregunta": "92",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Paris|Saint Germain",
      "pregunta": "93",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Southampton",
      "pregunta": "94",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "leicester",
      "pregunta": "95",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Boca Juniors",
      "pregunta": "96",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Hannover 96",
      "pregunta": "97",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Celta de Vigo",
      "pregunta": "98",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Watford",
      "pregunta": "99",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Escudos de fútbol",
      "respuesta": "Cagliari",
      "pregunta": "100",
      "categoria": "Escudos"
    }
  ]
}
